automotix.net 2006-06-18

# Automotix: Automotive Instant Exchange - License Agreement: Terms and Conditions

We understand that privacy is very important to you. This Privacy Statement tells you how we protect and use information that we collect through this Automotix web site. Automotix and its affiliates also operate other web sites. This Privacy Statement does may apply to the other Automotix web sites.

This Privacy Statement was last changed on April 25, 2006. We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. We recommend you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the web site.

By using the [www.automotix.net](http://www.automotix.net/) web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. Please read our Terms of Use to understand the general rules about your use of this web site. Except as written in any other disclaimers, policies, terms of use, or other notices on this web site, this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use are the complete agreement between you and Automotix with respect to your use of this web site. You may be subject to additional terms that may apply when you access particular services or materials on certain areas in this web site, or by following a link from this web site.

**INTRODUCTION**

The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our web site. We collect and use your non-personal information (information that is not identifiable to you personally) differently than your personal information.

**WHAT IS NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Non-personal information is information we collect through this web site that does not identify you as an individual person. It may include information such as the following: 

  * web browser software you use
  * domain from which you access the Internet
  * IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our web site
  * date and time you access our web site
  * which pages you have visited on our web site
  * personal information that has been de-identified (for example: vehicle information, business type, city and state)

We may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of your computer when you visit. The cookie may be stored on your computer's hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information. We will not allow third parties to place cookies on our web site.

**WHAT DOES AUTOMOTIX DO WITH NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Because non-personal information cannot identify you or be tied to you in any way, there are no restrictions on the ways that we can use or share non-personal information. We are always looking for ways to better serve you and improve this web site. We will use non-personal information from you to help us make this web site more useful to visitors. We also will use non-personal information for other business purposes. For example, we may use non-personal information or aggregate de-identified personal information to: 

  * create reports for internal use to develop programs, products, services or content
  * customize the information or services that are of interest to you
  * share it with or sell it to third parties
  * provide aggregated "traffic statistics" and "response rates" to third parties

**WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Personal information is information we collect through this web site that we can use to specifically identify you, such as your: 

  * name
  * telephone number
  * e-mail address

In some places on this web site you have the opportunity to send us personal information about yourself. For example, you may fill out a part locator form, car finder search, or a feedback form.

**HOW DOES AUTOMOTIX KEEP AND USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We may keep and use personal information we collect from you through this web site to provide you with access to this web site. In addition, we may keep and use your personal information: 

  * to distribute to potential sellers
  * to respond to your inquiries
  * to personalize your access to our web site, for example, by telling you about new features that may be of interest to you
  * to contact you with information that might be of interest to you, including information about promotional products and services of ours and of others
  * for analytical purposes and to research, develop and improve programs, products, services and content
  * to enforce this Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of this web site
  * to protect our rights or property
  * to comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process

**DOES AUTOMOTIX EVER SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

Automotix will not share your personal information collected from this web site with an unrelated third party without your permission, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement.

In the ordinary course of business, we will share some personal information with sellers that may stock the part or the vehicle you are looking for. In all cases in which we share your personal information with a third party, we will not authorize them to keep, disclose or use your information with others except for the purpose of providing the services we asked them to provide. 

We will not sell, exchange or publish your personal information, except in conjunction with a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, or acquisition.

We may be legally compelled to release your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting web site visitors who violate our rules or engage in behavior which is harmful to other visitors (or illegal).

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we feel that the disclosure is necessary to: 

  * enforce this Privacy Statement and the other rules about your use of this web site
  * protect our rights or property
  * comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process

**WHAT HAPPENS IF THE PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES?**

We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. We recommend you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the web site.

Recent revisions to the Privacy Statement:

Our Privacy Statement was significantly expanded on April 25, 2006.

**WHAT ABOUT PRIVACY ON OTHER WEB SITES?**

This web site may contain links to other web sites. Some of those web sites may be operated by Automotix, and some may be operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of web sites operated by others. This Privacy Statement does not apply to any other web site, even the other Automotix web sites. We are not responsible for the performance of web sites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you leave this web site we recommend that you review each web site's privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices. 

**DOES AUTOMOTIX EVER COMMUNICATE DIRECTLY WITH VISITORS TO THIS WEB SITE?**

We may contact you periodically by e-mail, mail or telephone to provide information regarding programs, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. In addition, some of the features on this web site allow you to communicate with us using an online form. If your communication requests a response from us, we will send you a response via e-mail. The e-mail response or confirmation may include your personal information, including personal information about your vehicle, your name, address, etc. We cannot guarantee that our e-mails to you will be secure from unauthorized interception. 

**WHAT ABOUT WEB SITE SECURITY?**

We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

**HOW TO CONTACT AUTOMOTIX?**

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please use the Contact Automotix link at the top of your screen or contact us at:

Automotix LLc  
5925 Nall Avenue, Suite 400  
Mission, KS 66202-3403  
Phone: 913-236-9629
